[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_v2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9901_0008_d_00_container_oldstoneremembers_v2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_8",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_v2_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0008_oldstoneremembers",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9901_0008_d_00_container_oldstoneremembers",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_8",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0008_oldstoneremembers_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseEventTags": "HFR"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0009_thetower",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9901_0009_d_00_container_thetower",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_9",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_8",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0009_thetower_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0009_thetower_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0009_thetower_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0009_thetower_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0009_thetower_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0009_thetower_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0009_thetower_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0010_inthequiet",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9901_0010_d_00_container_inthequiet",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_9",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0010_inthequiet_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0010_inthequiet_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0010_inthequiet_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0010_inthequiet_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0010_inthequiet_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0010_inthequiet_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0010_inthequiet_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0011_afreshsoul_V2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9901_0011_d_00_container_afreshsoul_V2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_10",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0011_afreshsoul_V2_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0011_afreshsoul",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9901_0011_d_00_container_afreshsoul",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_10",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0011_afreshsoul_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0011_afreshsoul_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseEventTags": "HFR"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0012_overseaunderstone",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9901_0012_d_00_container_overseaunderstone",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0012_overseaunderstone_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0012_overseaunderstone_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0012_overseaunderstone_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0012_overseaunderstone_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0012_overseaunderstone_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0012_overseaunderstone_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0012_overseaunderstone_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0013_argentandaether",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9901_0013_d_00_container_argentandaether",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_13",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0013_argentandaether_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0013_argentandaether_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0013_argentandaether_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0013_argentandaether_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0013_argentandaether_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0013_argentandaether_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0013_argentandaether_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0014_oldfoesoldfavors",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 16,
        "Task": "9901_0014_d_00_container_oldfoesoldfavors",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902_MSQ_Adiana",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_14",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0014_oldfoesoldfavors_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0014_oldfoesoldfavors_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0014_oldfoesoldfavors_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0014_oldfoesoldfavors_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0014_oldfoesoldfavors_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0014_oldfoesoldfavors_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0014_oldfoesoldfavors_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0015_itmustflow",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "Task": "9902_0015_d_00_container_itmustflow",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902_MSQ_Adiana",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_14",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0015_itmustflow_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0015_itmustflow_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0015_itmustflow_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0015_itmustflow_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0015_itmustflow_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0015_itmustflow_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0015_itmustflow_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0016_corruptiontincture",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 18,
        "Task": "9902_0016_d_00_container_corruptiontincture",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902_MSQ_Adiana",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_15",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0016_corruptiontincture_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0016_corruptiontincture_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0016_corruptiontincture_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0016_corruptiontincture_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0016_corruptiontincture_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0016_corruptiontincture_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0016_corruptiontincture_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0017_landcriesout",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9902_0017_d_00_container_landcriesout",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902_MSQ_Adiana",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_16",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0017_landcriesout_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9902_0018_returntoyonas",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0017_landcriesout_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0017_landcriesout_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0017_landcriesout_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0017_landcriesout_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0017_landcriesout_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0017_landcriesout_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0018_returntoyonas",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 19,
        "Task": "9902_0018_d_00_container_returntoyonas",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_17",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0018_returntoyonas_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0018_returntoyonas_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0018_returntoyonas_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0018_returntoyonas_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0018_returntoyonas_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0018_returntoyonas_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0018_returntoyonas_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0019_forgethestaff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 23,
        "Task": "9901_0019_d_00_container_forgethestaff",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_18",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0019_forgethestaff_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9901_0019_forgethestaffreturn",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0019_forgethestaff_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0019_forgethestaff_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0019_forgethestaff_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0019_forgethestaff_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0019_forgethestaff_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0019_forgethestaff_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0019_forgethestaffreturn",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 23,
        "Task": "9901_0019_d_00_container_forgethestaffreturn",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_19a",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_19",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0019_forgethestaffreturn_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0019_forgethestaff_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0018_returntoyonas_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0019_forgethestaff_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0019_forgethestaff_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0019_forgethestaff_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0019_forgethestaff_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0020_healtherift",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9901_0020_d_00_container_healtherift",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_19a",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0020_healtherift_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0020_healtherift_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0020_healtherift_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0020_healtherift_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0020_healtherift_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0020_healtherift_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0020_healtherift_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0021_destinyunearthed",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "Task": "9901_0021_d_00_container_destinyunearthed",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0021_destinyunearthed_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0021_destinyunearthed_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0021_destinyunearthed_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0021_destinyunearthed_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0021_destinyunearthed_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0021_destinyunearthed_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0021_destinyunearthed_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0022_theritual",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "Task": "9901_0022_d_00_container_theritual",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9901_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_21",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0022_theritual_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0022_theritual_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0022_theritual_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0022_theritual_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0022_theritual_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0022_theritual_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0022_theritual_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0023_agreatmovement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 26,
        "Task": "9901_0023_d_00_container_agreatmovement",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903_MSQ_Emile",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_23",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_22",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0023_agreatmovement_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0023_agreatmovement_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0023_agreatmovement_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0023_agreatmovement_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0023_agreatmovement_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0023_agreatmovement_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0023_agreatmovement_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0024_alostcause",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9903_0024_d_00_container_alostcause",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903_MSQ_Emile",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_24",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_23",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0024_alostcause_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9903_0024_alostcause_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9903_0024_alostcause_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_0024_alostcause_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9903_0024_alostcause_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9903_0024_alostcause_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9903_0024_alostcause_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0025_chainofcommand",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9903_0025_d_00_container_chainofcommand",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903_MSQ_Emile",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_24",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0025_chainofcommand_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9903_0025_chainofcommand_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9903_0025_chainofcommand_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_0025_chainofcommand_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9903_0025_chainofcommand_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9903_0025_chainofcommand_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9903_0025_chainofcommand_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0026_heartsandsouls",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9903_0026_d_00_container_heartsandsouls",
        "NpcDestinationId": "NPC_9902_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_26",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_25",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0026_heartsandsouls_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9903_0026_heartsandsouls_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9903_0026_heartsandsouls_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_0026_heartsandsouls_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9903_0026_heartsandsouls_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9903_0026_heartsandsouls_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9903_0026_heartsandsouls_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0027_thesyndicatesupport",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 30,
        "Task": "9901_0027_d_00_container_thesyndicatesupport",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9904_MSQ_Theophrastus",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_26",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0027_thesyndicatesupport_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0027_thesyndicatesupport_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0027_thesyndicatesupport_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0027_thesyndicatesupport_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0027_thesyndicatesupport_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0027_thesyndicatesupport_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0027_thesyndicatesupport_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknows",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknows",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9914_MSQ_Hunter",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknows_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsa",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsa",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknowsa",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9915_MSQ_Researcher1",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27c",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27b",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsb",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknows_V2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknows_V2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9914_MSQ_Hunter",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknows_V2_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_V2",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseEventTags": "HFR"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_V2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknowsa_V2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9915_MSQ_Researcher1",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27c",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27b",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_V2_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsb",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseEventTags": "HFR"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsb",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknowsb",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9916_MSQ_Researcher2",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27d",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27c",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsb_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsc",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsb_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsb_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsb_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsb_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsb_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsc",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknowsc",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9917_MSQ_Researcher3",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27e",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27d",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsc_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsd",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsc_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsc_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsc_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsc_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsc_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsd",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknowsd",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9918_MSQ_Researcher4",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27f",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27e",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsd_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowse",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsd_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsd_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsd_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsd_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsd_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknowse",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknowse",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9904_MSQ_Theophrastus",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_28",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27f",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknowse_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowse_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0028_thenoseknows_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowse_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowse_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowse_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowse_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0029_thestormwall",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9904_0029_d_00_container_thestormwall",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9904_MSQ_Theophrastus",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_29",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_28",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0029_thestormwall_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0029_thestormwall_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0029_thestormwall_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0029_thestormwall_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0029_thestormwall_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0029_thestormwall_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0029_thestormwall_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0030_twodown",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9904_0030_d_00_container_twodown",
        "NpcDestinationId": "NPC_9902_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_30",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_29",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0030_twodown_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0030_twodown_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0030_twodown_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0030_twodown_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0030_twodown_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0030_twodown_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0030_twodown_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0031_themaraudersupport",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "Task": "9901_0031_d_00_container_themaraudersupport",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905_MSQ_Rima",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_31",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_30",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0031_themaraudersupport_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0031_themaraudersupport_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0031_themaraudersupport_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0031_themaraudersupport_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0031_themaraudersupport_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0031_themaraudersupport_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0031_themaraudersupport_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0032_invalhalla",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 36,
        "Task": "9905_0032_d_00_container_invalhalla",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905_MSQ_Rima",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_32",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_31",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0032_invalhalla_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0032_invalhalla_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0032_invalhalla_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0032_invalhalla_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0032_invalhalla_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0032_invalhalla_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0032_invalhalla_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0033_stillwerise",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9905_0033_d_00_container_stillwerise",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905_MSQ_Rima",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_33",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_32",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0033_stillwerise_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0033_stillwerise_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0033_stillwerise_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0033_stillwerise_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0033_stillwerise_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0033_stillwerise_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0033_stillwerise_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0034_thealliance",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9905_0034_d_00_container_thealliance",
        "NpcDestinationId": "NPC_9902_MSQ_Yonas",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_33",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0034_thealliance_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0034_thealliance_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0034_thealliance_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0034_thealliance_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0034_thealliance_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0034_thealliance_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0034_thealliance_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0035_herewestand",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "Task": "9901_0035_d_00_container_herewestand",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9919_MSQ_WardenScout",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_35",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_34",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0035_herewestand_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0035_herewestand_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0035_herewestand_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0035_herewestand_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0035_herewestand_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0035_herewestand_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0035_herewestand_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "Task": "9901_0036_d_00_container_masterofthetempest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9919_MSQ_WardenScout",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_36",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_35",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0036_masterofthetempest_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9919_0037_planb",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9919_0037_d_00_container_planb",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905c_MSQ_Rima",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_37",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_36",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9919_0037_planb_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9919_0037_planb_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9919_0037_planb_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9919_0037_planb_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9919_0037_planb_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9919_0037_planb_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0037_planb_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0038_itstrueface",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 42,
        "Task": "9905_0038_d_00_container_itstrueface",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903c_MSQ_Emile",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_38",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_37",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0038_itstrueface_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0038_itstrueface_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0039_aherosduty",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 43,
        "Task": "9903_0039_d_00_container_aherosduty",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903c_MSQ_Emile",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_39",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_38",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0039_aherosduty_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9903_0039_aherosduty_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0040_emilesrequest",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 44,
        "Task": "9903_0040_d_00_container_emilesrequest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903d_MSQ_Emile",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_40",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_39",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0040_emilesrequest_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9903_0040_emilesrequest_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0041_somethinglefttosave",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9903_0041_d_00_container_somethinglefttosave",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903d_MSQ_Emile",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_41",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_40",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0042_shecameback",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 46,
        "Task": "9905_0042_d_00_container_shecameback",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905d_MSQ_Rima",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_42",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_41",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0042_shecameback_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0042_shecameback_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0042_shecameback_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0042_shecameback_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0042_shecameback_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0042_shecameback_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0042_shecameback_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0043_foragoodcause",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 47,
        "Task": "9905_0043_d_00_container_foragoodcause",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9909_MSQ_AEVillager3",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_43",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_42",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0043_foragoodcause_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0043_foragoodcause_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9909_0044_mothertongue",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 48,
        "Task": "9909_0044_d_00_container_mothertongue",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905d_MSQ_Rima",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_44",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_43",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9909_0044_mothertongue_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9909_0044_mothertongue_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0045_thebox",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 50,
        "Task": "9905_0045_d_00_container_thebox",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_45",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_44",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0045_thebox_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9905_0045_thebox_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9905_0045_thebox_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_0045_thebox_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9905_0045_thebox_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9905_0045_thebox_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9905_0045_thebox_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0046_stemthetide",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9902_0046_d_00_container_stemthetide",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_46",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_45",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0046_stemthetide_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0046_stemthetide_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0047_greatminds",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 51,
        "Task": "9904_0047_d_00_container_greatminds",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9904d_MSQ_Theophrastus",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_47",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_46",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0047_greatminds_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0047_greatminds_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0047_greatminds_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0047_greatminds_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0047_greatminds_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0047_greatminds_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0047_greatminds_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 52,
        "Task": "9904_0048_d_00_container_enemyofmyenemy",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_48",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_47",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0049_recipeforfailure",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 53,
        "Task": "9902_0049_d_00_container_recipeforfailure",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_49",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_48",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0049_recipeforfailure_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0049_recipeforfailure_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9906_0050_thescenicroute",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "Task": "9906_0050_d_00_container_thescenicroute",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_50",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_49",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9906_0050_thescenicroute_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicroute_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9906_0051_ararespice",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9906_0051_d_00_container_ararespice",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_50b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_50",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9906_0051_ararespice_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9906_0051_ararespice_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9906_0051_ararespice_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9906_0051_ararespice_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9906_0051_ararespice_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9906_0051_ararespice_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9906_0051_ararespice_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "Task": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_51",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_50b",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0052_saboteur",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "Task": "9902_0052_d_00_container_saboteur",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_51",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0052_saboteur_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0052_saboteur_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0052_saboteur_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0052_saboteur_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0052_saboteur_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0052_saboteur_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0052_saboteur_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52a",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth_Task1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9907_MSQ_AEVillager1",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth_Task2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9908_MSQ_AEVillager2",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52c",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth_Task3",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_53",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0054_ASelflessNature",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "Task": "9902_0054_d_00_container_ASelflessNature",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_54",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52a",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0054_ASelflessNature_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0054_richesoftheearth_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0054_richesoftheearth_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0054_richesoftheearth_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0054_richesoftheearth_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_54_richesoftheearth_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0054_richesoftheearth_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0055_shatteredmountain",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "Task": "9902_0055_d_00_container_shatteredmountain",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9910_MSQ_AEScout",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_55",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_54",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0055_shatteredmountain_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9902_0055_shatteredmountain_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9910_0056_thetempestsheart",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "Task": "9910_0056_d_00_container_thetempestsheart",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0717_Warden",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_56",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_55",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9910_0056_thetempestsheart_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9910_0056_thetempestsheart_complete_available_response_alt",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0057_insoulinstone",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "Task": "9901_0057_d_00_container_insoulinstone",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0717_Warden",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_57",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_56",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0057_insoulinstone_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9901_0057_insoulinstone_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9901_0057_insoulinstone_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_0057_insoulinstone_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9901_0057_insoulinstone_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9901_0057_insoulinstone_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9901_0057_insoulinstone_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseEventTags": "MSQ"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9910_0058_finallyexhale",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "Task": "9910_0058_d_00_container_finallyexhale",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905e_MSQ_Rima",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_58",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_57",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9910_0058_finallyexhale_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9910_0058_finallyexhale_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseEventTags": "MSQ"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "Task": "9926_0101_d_00_container_TenaciousRose",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9926_VK_AbigailRoseB",
        "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0101",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9926_0101_TenaciousRose_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9927_0102_VisionsOfInvaders",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "Task": "9927_0102_d_00_container_VisionsOfInvaders",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0903_Survivalist",
        "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0102",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9927_0102_VisionsOfInvaders_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@9927_0102_VisionsOfInvaders_objective_title",
        "Description": "@9927_0102_VisionsOfInvaders_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9927_0102_VisionsOfInvaders_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9927_0102_VisionsOfInvaders_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9927_0102_VisionsOfInvaders_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9927_0102_VisionsOfInvaders_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    }
]